onlinebusinessbuildingsuccess.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy Policy

**\- PRIVACY POLICY -  
** THIS IS IMPORTANT -- PLEASE READ ****

##### We are strongly committed to safeguarding our subscribers' privacy and operate under the following strict privacy policy.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED:

### The only information we obtain about our subscribers is information that is needed to allow you to participate within the website.  This includes but is not limited to the following:

### 1\. Logging in to the website itself.

### 2\. Logging into any and all forums within the website at any level.

### 3. Logging into any and all chat rooms within the website at any level.

### 4. Proccessing any credit card charges for subscription dues including any recurring charges. 

### 7\. The transfering of information between subscriber and any 'Approved'* Life Coach needed to facilitate a one on one coaching session.

### 8.  Using the 'contact us' form. 

### The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made available to the general public for any reason without the expressed consent of the subscriber.  Personally identifiable information provided by subscribers (name, email or home address, phone numbers etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business including other subscribers of this website with the exception of an 'approved' representative of this site while accomplishing assigned tasks in which subscriber has previously agreed to. 

### COOKIES:  

### Each time a subscriber logs into this site, we store a temporary 'cookie' in the browser files of that subscriber's computer. This cookie is used during your online session to allow you free access to the subscribers area, without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password.  When you log off or leave the site, the cookies file is automatically removed. 

### EXTERNAL LINKS:  

### In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third party websites. In no case is subscriber information or 'cookies' provided to the third party sites. However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser. 

### PRIVATE FORUMS:

### We provide our subscribers with a multi-tiered discussion forum boards that makes sharing information with other subscribers easy. To protect your privacy when posting or replying to messages in the message board, your personal information and email is not revealed. However, remember that any information you disclose in the message board areas can be read by all other subscribers, so exercise caution and your own discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### OPT-IN FORM:  

### Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us.  In accordance to the [CAN-SPAM act.](http://www.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/canspam.html) we provide a way to unsubscribe from our mailing list on each and every email we send that is covered by the CAN-SPAM act.  You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose without your expressed consent. To insure the validity of your choice to subscribe to out mailing list we choose to use a double option system in which you must confirm your desire to recieve information from us.  The date, time, IP address , and the  webpage in which  you intitially requested information is recorded in the event of dispute about having permission to send you information.   

### If you have questions regarding our privacy policy please feel free to [Contact Me.](mailto:dan@onlinebusinessbuildingsuccess.com)
